NGUYỄN DUY TÀI

Software Engineer



Contact information

- <u></u> 24/06/1993
- Male
- 0903754393
- □ nguyenduytaihp93@gmail.com
- A Hanoi, Vietnam
- Skype: underwaterhp93
 Github:https://github.com/TaiNguyen2406

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a fullstack developer and have worked on software development for 6 years

Have a strong experience working with dedicated projects. Proven ability to work independently as well as in teamwork. Good at cross teamwork.

Willing to learn and quickly adapt to new technology and new environment.

Active, able to work under high pressure. Be self-motivated, creative, and enthusiastic about working.

https://tainguyen2406.github.io/tainguyencv/

Education

Vietnam Maritime University

Sep 2012-Feb 2016

Major: Information Techonoly/ Software development

GPA: 3.05/4

Work experience

Software engineer

JUNE 2021-NOW

TRAPETS (scandinavian software park)

Main responsibilities:

- Developing microservices using .net core and MS SQL, MongoDB
- Creating CI/CD using Docker, Kubernetes, Azure DevOps
- Build a front end site using Angular

Software engineer

April 2019-June 2021

Episerver Vietnam

Main responsibilities:

- Developing microservices using .net core and CosmosDB (NoSQL)
- Creating CI/CD using Docker, Kubernetes, Azure DevOps, Bedrock
- Creating a client site using ReactJs, HTML, CSS
- Converting products of Episerver to the new platform.(Net framework to Net Core/ReactJS)

.Net Developer

June 2018-April 2019

Nittsu System Vietnam

Main responsibilities:

- Developing web application, web api using .net framework, javascript and Microsoft SQL

.Net Developer

Jan 2016-June 2018

BaoAn JSC

Main responsibilities:

- Developing windows app, web application, web api using .net framework (C# and VB.net) and Microsoft SQL
- Testing and deploying the product

Honors & Awards

2013-2014: VIMARU Scholarship in 2nd semester 2013-2014 and 2nd semester 2014-2015.

2016-2017: Promising young employees of Bao An Company

2016-2017: Episerver On-the-spot awards

Certifications

2014: TOEIC Certificate with score 595 issued by VIMARU